Greece
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Greece
2.1.1.2.5
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1323
- Greece, 2.1.1.2.5
  - Old Greek pointing down to Athens, circa 1918; 20; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Old Greek talking to son at Acropolis, Athens, circa 1918; 21; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Ruins at Athens, circa 1918; 22; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Lowell Thomas and Harry Chase in front of the Parthenon, Athens, circa 1918; 23; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Temple of Thesus, Athens, circa 1918; 24; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Soldiers and tents in front of the Temple of Thesus, Athens, circa 1918; 25; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Looking down on olive orchard, circa 1918; 26; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Big tree on road through Greece, circa 1918; 27; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Four Greek mountaineers, circa 1918; 28; 5x7 film (Box 1323)
  - Diogenes on donkey, circa 1918; 29; 5x7 film (Box 1323)
  - Demosthenes man, circa 1918; 30; 5x7 film (Box 1323)
  - Old Greek man and daughter, circa 1918; 31; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Two boys in traditional Greek clothes, dancing for crowd, circa 1918; 32; 5x7 film (Box 1323)
  - Serbian boy, circa 1918; 33; 5x7 film (Box 1323)
  - Man, in traditional costume, with woman and child, circa 1918; 34; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Group of Greeks at fair, circa 1918; 35; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Greek fair, circa 1918; 36; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Man in traditional Greek costume sharing water with old man in shorts, circa 1918; 37; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Man in traditional Greek costume talking to three soldiers, others nearby them, circa 1918; 38; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Essed Pasha, with dog, circa 1918; 39; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Russian diplomat in Serbian army at Salonica, circa 1918; 40; 5x7 film (Box 1323)
  - Panorama of Salonica, circa 1918; 41; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - View of Salonica from top of hill, boy and Lowell Thomas [?] in foreground, circa 1918; 42; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Mound at Salonica, circa 1918; 43; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Salonica street scene, circa 1918; 44; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Bralos, tents and soldiers in foreground, circa 1918; 45; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Tents on hillside, soldier in foreground, circa 1918; 46; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Winding military road through mountains, soldier sitting on rock at right, circa 1918; 47; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Janes Club, soldier by building, automobile at left, Macedonia, circa 1918; 48; 5x7 (Box 1323)